lovebscott.com 2014-12-31

# Privacy Policy | B. Scott | Celebrity Entertainment News, Fashion, Music and Advice

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, LoveBScott.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting LoveBScott.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Notice Regarding Online behavioural Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information  
when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information  
(e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked  
or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These  
companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn  
more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To  
opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

**Disclaimer** : This site does not claim any ownership of any of the media (music, videos, etc.) presented on this site. The media presented is intended for promotional use only.

All images on lovebscott.com are readily available on the internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be published according to the U.S Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

If you are the copyright owner and would like your media removed, please contact denver@lovebscott.com.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of lovebscott.com then you may contact us at bscott@lovebscott.com

Last updated, 06 January 2014.
